Destroyer Yukikaze
First Fleet
Flagship Kirishima
Signal round sighted from vanguard ship Yukikaze.
IDENTIFIED
UN Cosmo Force Far East Sector Headquarters
At 1200, the First Fleet encountered the enemy
Mars, Remains of Arcadia Port
Three Weeks Later
Passing Through Polluted Zone
Enemy Plant Emitting Poison
Born July 7th 2178 (age 20)
Seventh Space Tactical Division
Rank: Third Lieutenant
Susumu Kodai
Yamato Plan Crew List
TOP SECRET
Episode 1
Messenger of Iscandar
Believe
A star will shine today
Above your head
Even far away
It pours down onto us
The same brilliance
Surely it is the way to return
A small hope to light it up
To the sky you gaze upon
If I pray to eternity for a connection
Even in days of sorrow
Can we meet once again?
The heart knows it is all right
Will it be a mutual promise?